<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>WiredPlane</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>support@wiredplane.com</Address_1>
        <Address_2>support@wiredplane.com</Address_2>
        <City_Town>Moscow</City_Town>
        <State_Province />
        <Zip_Postal_Code />
        <Country>Russia</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.wiredplane.com/</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Ilja</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Razinkov</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>support@wiredplane.com</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name />
        <Contact_Last_Name />
        <Contact_Email>support@wiredplane.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>sales@wiredplane.com</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>support@wiredplane.com</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>support@wiredplane.com</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone />
        <Support_Phone />
        <General_Phone />
        <Fax_Phone />
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>WPBackup</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>1.0</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>10</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>10</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2004</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>20.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code>RUR</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
        <Program_Cost_Other>200</Program_Cost_Other>
        <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win98,WinME,WinNT 3.x,WinNT 4.x,WinXP,Windows2000</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English,Russian</Program_Language>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>WPBackup.zip</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous>WPBackup.zip</Filename_Previous>
        <Filename_Generic>WPBackup.zip</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>WPBackup.zip</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>252969</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>247</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>0.25</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count>14</Expire_Count>
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Change_Info />
        <Program_Specific_Category>Miscellaneous</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_Categories>Clipboard, Hotkey manager</Program_Categories>
        <Program_System_Requirements>If your Windows works fine - this is enough</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>Backup, snapshot</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Folder snapshot based backup utility</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>Folder snapshot based backup utility (command-line tool, single exe file)</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>Folder snapshot based backup utility (command-line tool, single exe file)</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>Folder snapshot based backup utility (command-line tool, single exe file)</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>Folder snapshot based backup utility (command-line tool, single exe file)</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://www.wiredplane.com/wpt-wpbackup/info.shtml</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL>http://www.wiredplane.com/order.shtml?who=wpbackup</Application_Order_URL>
        <Application_Screenshot_URL />
        <Application_Icon_URL />
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.wiredplane.com/wpt-wpbackup/pad_file.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://www.wiredplane.com/download/wpbackup.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>WPBackup is distributed as Freeware.
See documentation or visit our web site for more information.
You can distribute installation package without ANY modifications to its content</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>WIREDPLANE.com END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT 

PLEASE CAREFULLY READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS BEFORE USING THIS 
PRODUCT. IT CONTAINS SOFTWARE, THE USE OF WHICH IS LICENSED BY WIREDPLANE.com 
TO ITS CUSTOMERS FOR THEIR USE ONLY AS SET FORTH BELOW. BY DOWNLOADING THE 
SOFTWARE, OPENING THE MEDIA PACKAGE, INSTALLING THE SOFTWARE ON YOUR COMPUTER, 
OR BY ENTERING A REGISTRATION NUMBER TO ACTIVATE IT, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY 
ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE 
TERMS, YOU MUST PROMPTLY DESTROY ALL COPIES OF THE SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING 
DOCUMENTATION. USING ANY PART OF THE SOFTWARE INDICATES THAT YOU ACCEPT THESE 
TERMS AND CONDITIONS. 

1. In this agreement, &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable Software 
program. The term &quot;Software&quot; shall also include any upgrades, modified versions, 
updates, additions, and copies of the Software licensed to you by WiredPlane 
labs. 

2. All copyrights to this software are exclusively owned by the author - 
Razinkov Ilja - and WiredPlane.com. All title and copyrights in and to the 
Software, as well as any backup copy made by you, are owned by WiredPlane.com 
and may be protected by applicable copyright or other intellectual property laws 
and treaties. Except as stated above, this agreement does not grant you any 
rights to patents, trade secrets, trademarks, copyrights or any other rights in 
respect of the Software. 

3. This software is distributed on a Freeware basis (also known as 
'Try-before-you-buy'). The software may be freely distributed, added to any CD 
compilation or online software repository, provided the distribution package is 
not modified. No person or company may charge a fee for the distribution of this 
software without written permission from the copyright holder. 

4. Skipped

5. Product maintenance. WiredPlane.com is not obligated to provide you with 
maintenance or updates for the Software. However, any maintenance or updates 
provided by WiredPlane.com shall be covered by this agreement. 

6. You may not alter this software in any way. You are also not allowed to 
emulate, decompile, disassemble or attempting to discover the source code, 
otherwise reverse engineer any executable part of original package. Any such 
unauthorized use shall result in immediate and automatic termination of this 
license and may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. 

7. Disclaimer of warranty: THIS SOFTWARE IS DISTRIBUTED &quot;AS IS&quot;. NO WARRANTY OF 
ANY KIND IS EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. YOU USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK. WE MAY NOT BE 
HELD LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, 
PUNITIVE, OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES 
FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS 
INFORMATION) OR ANY OTHER KIND OF LOSS WHILE USING OR MISUSING THIS SOFTWARE. 

8. This license shall terminate automatically if you fail to comply with the 
limitations described in this Agreement. No notice shall be required from 
WiredPlane.com. to effectuate such termination. On termination you must destroy 
all copies of the Software. 

9. All rights not expressly granted here are reserved by Razinkov Ilja and 
WiredPlane.com. 

10. Installing and using this software signifies acceptance of these terms and 
conditions of the license. If you do not agree with the terms of this license 
you must remove this software from your storage devices and cease to use the 
product.</EULA>
</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
